Mihai Elisei

Phone No.: +353 (0)89 276 1806 Email: mihai.m.elisei@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mihai-elisei-48ba87a7/

GitHub: https://github.com/MihaiElisei

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly motivated and organized individual, committed to excellent service with the ability to multitask at the highest level. Flexible work ethic with 5+ years' experience within the IT sector, delivering a quality service with integrity. Strong organisational and time management skills. Highly computer literate with the ability to learn and absorb technical details and systems very quickly. Presently upskilling to further career in a role as a junior software developer.

KEY SKILLS

• **Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python.

Databases: MySQL
Version Control: GitHub, Git
Frameworks: Bootstrap

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

April 2022 – present Code Institute

Diploma in Full Stack Software Development (E-Commerce) Credit Rated by The University of the West of Scotland

October 2019 – present Oil & Gas University

Oil & Gas Engineering (Part-time)

Ploiesti Romania

September 2008 – august 2010 Advanced/Higher Certificate in Mechanic Foreman

Military school of warrant officers of the Romanian Naval Forces

Constanta Romania

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

1. **Transport Services** – Code Institute project. Website for a small company.

GitHub - https://github.com/MihaiElisei/transport-services.git

Technologies Used - HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap.

2. Player vs. Player – Code Institute project. Interactive multiplayer game.

GitHub - https://github.com/MihaiElisei/Player-vs.-Player.git

Technologies Used - HTML5 , CSS, JavaScript.

WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2022 – present IT Support Engineer, Convergint Technologies, Dublin, Ireland

- Installation and Commissioning of Cameras, controllers, panels, sensors, & devices;
- Overlook the project installation and making sure that it meets the technical design;
- Data entry and programming in various cloud based applications;

Dec 2021 – May 2022 Field Engineer, Actavo, Dublin, Ireland

- Install and service cabling infrastructure and devices for Data, Audio Visual, and CCTV; includes prewiring, installation, termination, testing, reporting, and labelling per specifications and drawings;
- Interact with customers and prospects, ensuring all inquiries are handled professionally;
- Perform additional duties and projects as assigned;

September 2017 – October 2021

IT Technician, Ministry of Justice Romania National Administration of Penitentiaries.

- Install and service cabling infrastructure and devices for Data, Audio Visual, and CCTV; includes prewiring, installation, termination, testing, reporting, and labelling per specifications and drawings;
- Test Quality of lines, as well as broadband quality;
- Used good problem-solving skills for troubleshooting problems;
- Administration of Windows based applications of basic principles, theories, and concepts;
- Speak and communicate effectively with other members of the jobsite crew;

August 2010 – August 2017

Warrant Officer Romanian Navy

- Interactive communication;
- Performing high productivity processing, assembly of machine tools;
- Checking products quality;
- Providing the observance of the occupational protection norms and firefighting norms;

CERTIFICATES

- Udemy Complete JavaScript (40/69 hours)
- Udemy The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp (10/20 hours)
- Udemy React-The complete guide(incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)(5/48 hours)
- Pirple Python3 Fundamentals (3/16 hours)

•